https://www.beaconcollege.edu/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
MENUMENUAbout
Beacon At A Glance
The Beacon DifferenceMission StatementBeacon College Fact BookA Quick Guide To Beacon College
Office of the President
President’s WelcomeLeadershipPresident’s InitiativesBoard of TrusteesStrategic PlanAccreditation StatementPresident’s BiographyContact President's Office
Featured AdministratorsEmploymentCommunity OutreachBeacon College HistoryThe Life AbundantContact Us
Campus
LocationLiving EnvironmentsMason Art GalleryCollege BookstoreFitness CenterProposed Academic CenterCampus TourCampus Directory
Admissions
ApplyFor Students
New ApplicantsVisiting Student ProgramTransfer StudentsInternational StudentsAccepted Students
New Student Orientation at Beacon College
For ParentsFor EducatorsTuition & Financial Aid
Tuition & Fees
Tuition Comparison TableTuition Tax DeductionNet Price Calculator
Financial Aid
CARES Act Application and ProcessApplying for Financial AidFinancial Aid Processing FormsFederal and State ProgramsBeacon-Funded ProgramsBright Minds ScholarshipsRaise.Me ScholarshipScholarshipsVeteransMedical Tax Deduction for Educational BenefitsPaying For CollegeFrequently Asked QuestionsStudent Rights & Responsibilities
Virtual Learning SeriesNavigator PREPJump Start Virtual SemesterSummer High School Program
Summer For Success Course Options
Contact AdmissionsVirtual Visit OpportunitiesVisit Beacon
Academics
Academic Majors
Academic StandardsCIP Codes for Academic Majors
FacultyResources
College CatalogAcademic CalendarLibrary
Success Services
Center for Student SuccessMathematics LabWriting CenterCounseling
Career Development Center
Mission, Vision, and ValuesCareer Center ServicesSteps For Success10 Essential Employability SkillsCareers By MajorThe Internship ProcessOn-Campus EmploymentFamily Guide to Career DevelopmentCareer Development News
Registrar’s Office
Student Life
Housing
Housing Options & Application
DiningActivities
Activities and EventsClubs and Organizations
Health
Health FormsStudent Health Insurance
FitnessCommunity
Community Services
Transportation
Airport Shuttle Reservation FormTitle VI Transportation RightsReasonable Modification Policy
Safety
Emergency Preparedness
Office of Student Services
Title IX Information and ResourcesStudent HandbookStudent Forms
News & Events
COVID-19 Information CenterBeacon NewsParents WeekendCalendarsBeacon TV – "A World of Difference"The Beacon Salon SeriesRadio BeaconNewsletterVideo GalleryOffice of Communications
For The Media
Alumni
Alumni AssociationAlumni CouncilAlumni Giving
Giving
Beacon Community Acts FundVirtual Friends FundraiserCapital CampaignDonate NowGiving FAQOffice of Institutional Advancement
Capital Campaign
About Beacon College
Beacon At A Glance
The Beacon Difference
Mission Statement
Office of the President
President's Welcome
Leadership
Campus Directory
Beacon College is committed to keeping all personal information collected from visitors to our web site secure and private, and to meet or exceed existing privacy standards.
This Privacy Policy Agreement governs any and all data collection and usage in relation to Beacon College and the Beacon College website.  In using www.beaconcollege.edu, you are consenting to the data procedures outlined below.
Collection of Information
This website collects various types of information, such as:
Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, billing and/or credit card information, required when you make payments, donations, or complete any online form on the Beacon College web site. Beacon College needs this information to deliver the services you have requested.
Information automatically collected when visiting our website, include that obtained from cookies and third party tracking technologies.
Embedded content from other websites (e.g. videos, social media icons, interactive elements). Embedded content from other websites, such as YouTube, may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content.
Analytics tracking by Google and Facebook to monitor site usage and search engine accessibility.
Server logs which automatically collect the IP address, operating system, and page visited for every request to the web site.
Where We Send Your Data
Beacon College does not share your data with third parties without your permission.
Some form data is stored in the databases managed by the third party company providing the form app (including online application, donations, and some signup forms) and may include Wufoo, Mindfire Inc., QGiv, and DonorPerfect. By submitting certain online forms to Beacon College, you agree to allow your data to be stored on third party servers.
Your Rights Over Your Data
Beacon College collects some personal data via its web site as required for the completion of online forms such as application, registration, information request, and other types of forms. This information is retained for the length of time necessary to process your request and provide you with the service requested.
Online form data is removed from the web site within 6 months of submission.
If you reside in the European Union, you may request an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Use of Information Collected
Beacon College may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request.
Beacon College does not sell, rent or lease our user’s data to any third parties.
Beacon College may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that our users may frequent in an effort to glean what types of services and/or products may be the most popular to customers or the general public. This includes Google Analytics and Facebook tracking.
Beacon College may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:
Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Beacon College and/or our website;
Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Beacon College; and
Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of https://www.beaconcollege.edu and/or the general public.
Children Under Age of 13
Beacon College does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our website does contain links to other websites. Beacon College does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.
Security
Beacon College takes every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal information under our control.
The company uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for authentication and private communications to provide simple and secure access and communication of all personal information. Security software is installed to protect the server and web site from unauthorized access.
Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement
Beacon College reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those changes to our website homepage at https://www.beaconcollege.edu, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Beacon College decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.
Acceptance of Terms
Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our site. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.
Email: kphillips@beaconcollege.edu
Telephone Number: 855-220-5374
Mailing Address:
